Guide to the Capital Planning Building Files and Records 1981-1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Capital Planning Building Files and Records
1981-1999
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 280
Washington State University. Capital Planning
25 Linear feet of shelf space 25 boxes
The collection consists of records pertaining to construction, remodeling, maintenance, and improvement of WSU buildings. Buildings included here include Science Hall, Todd Hall Addition, WSU Children's Center, Yakama Village, Food and Human Nutrition Facility, Tri-Cities University Center, and Beasley Coliseum.
A University Architect served as the construction officer at Washington State University from 1911 forward. The modern form of the office dates from 1947 when it became a full-time, staffed administrative department. In 1967 the University Architect office was renamed as Facilities Planning, and then to Facilities Development in 1993. In 2001 it was renamed as Capital Planning. While Capital Planning is responsible for major planning and development, smaller projects are conducted by Facilities Operations. Facilities Operations descended from the Physical Plant in 1998, which in turn descended from Building and Grounds in 1967. While each line of programs has existed separately, some migration in function has occurred over the years. The primary difference between Capital Planning and Facilities Operations is the cost of the project in question - initially items costing less than $1,000,000 were assigned to Fac Ops, and those costing more to CP. By 2009, this break point is between $1,500,000 and $2,000,000.
The collection consists of records pertaining to construction, remodeling, maintenance, and improvement of WSU buildings. Buildings included here include Science Hall, Todd Hall Addition, WSU Children's Center, Yakama Village, Food and Human Nutrition Facility, Tri-Cities University Center, and Beasley Coliseum.
The collection is maintained in the order in which it was received in the Archives from Capital Planning. The records are primarily ordered by building number, with a few small files for individual buildings at the end.
The majority of this collection is open and available for research use. A few files are marked as confidential or classified (these are primarily identified as Attorney General files or Issues and Claims files; please contact Capital Planning if you wish access to these) and access to those may be restricted. These files are labeled in this page as RESTRICTED, each box containing restricted material is so labeled, and individual restricted folders are stickered as such.
These Capital Planning Building Files and Records were transferred to Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections on March 19th, 2002 (UA 2002-03) by Annie (last name unrecorded) of Capital Planning.
The WSU Archives hold a number of other Capital Plannng collections; to locate these please view our Archives' Collections List and our Accessions List, looking for the various names under which this department has operated: University Architect, Facilities Planning, Facilities Development, Capital Planning.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Facilities Operations -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Physical Plant -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Department of Building and Grounds -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Capital Planning -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Capital Planning and Development -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Development -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University. University Architect -- Records and correspondence.; Washington State University -- Buildings -- History -- Archives.; Washington State University. Facilities Operations.; Washington State University. Physical Plant.; Washington State University. Department of Building and Grounds.; Washington State University. Capital Planning.; Washington State University. Capital Planning and Development.; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Development.; Washington State University. Department of Facilities Planning.; Washington State University. University Architect.
College buildings -- Washington (State)
Architecture; Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- Building 0032 - Science Hall Remodeling, Phase II
  - Budget 2/26/1986 - 6/24/1993 (Box 1)
  - Regents 1/8/1987 - 8/7/1990 (Box 1)
  - Mahan and Smith Correspondence 5/5/1982 - 5/16/1988 (Box 1)
  - S. G. Morin Correspondence C08967 6/29/1987 - 10/15/1987 (Box 1)
  - Construction Reports 6/6/1988 - 1/2/1992 (Box 1)
  - Concrete Tests 1/4/1989 - 12/27/1988 (Box 1)
  - Arbitration Correspondence 5/5/1992 - 10/8/1993 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence #10 11/1/1990 - 6/15/1993 (Box 1)
  - Decker/Fukui Architects (Decker Associates) General Correspondence #6 10/19/1990 - 12/8/1992 (Box 1)
  - Decker/Fukui Architects Contract File #3 C08470 11/1/1990 - 1/14/1993 (Box 1)
  - Bouten Construction General Correspondence #2 6/1/1990 - 11/17/1992 (Box 1)
  - Bouten Construction Contract File #3 C09267 10/27/1989 - 2/26/1993 (Box 1)
  - Statements of Compliance 8/11/1988 - 12/14/1989 (Box 1)
  - Rejected Bids - Electrical - Bid Date 4/21/1988 (Box 1)
  - Rejected Bids - Mechanical - Bid Date 4/21/1988 (Box 1)
  - Rejected Bids - General - Bid Date 4/28/1988 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence #9 5/1/1990 - 10/31/1990 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence #8 1/1/1990 - 4/30/1990 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence #7 6/1/1989 - 12/31/1989 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #6 1/1/1989 - 5/31/1989 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #5 3/1/1988 - 12/31/1988 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #4 7/1/1987 - 2/29/1988 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #3 12/1/1986 - 6/30/1987 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #2 6/1/1986 - 11/30/1986 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence #1 2/10/1983 - 5/31/1986 (Box 2)
  - Building Program May, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Building Program November, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Building Program December, 1985 (Box 2)
  - BIOS Exhibit Planning and Design Statement of Qualifications (Box 2)
  - Decker/Hobbs Fukui Davison Life Cycle Cost Analysis 12/9/1982 (Box 2)
  - Decker/Fukui Davison Schematic Design Phase Brochure November, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Decker/Fukui and BIOS Exhibit Program Review and Recommendations 8/6/1990 (Box 2)
  - Neudorfer Engineers, Inc. Test Report 1/27/1992 (Box 2)
  - Decker Fukui General Correspondence #5 1/1/1990 - 10/31/1990 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui General Correspondence #4 1/1/1989 - 12/31/1989 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui General Correspondence #3 7/1/1987 - 12/31/1988 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui General Correspondence #2 2/1/1987 - 6/30/1987 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui General Correspondence #1 11/20/1985 - 1/31/1987 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui Contract File #2 C08470 1/8/1988 - 10/31/1990 (Box 3)
  - Decker Fukui Contract File #1 C08470 3/1/1986 - 1/7/198 8 (Box 3)
  - Bouten Construction General Correspondence #1 6/1/1988 - 5/31/1990 (Box 3)
  - Bouten Construction Contract File #2 C09267 4/1/1989 - 10/31/1989 (Box 3)
  - Bouten Construction Contract File #1 C09267 4/1/1988 - 3/31/1989 (Box 3)
- Building 0055A - Todd Hall Addition
  - Budget 1/11/1983 - 5/17/1991 (Box 4)
  - Environmental Impact Statement 6/23/1988 - 7/21/1988 (Box 4)
  - Regents 11/4/1987 - 11/12/1990 (Box 4)
  - Burke/Lee, A Joint Venture Correspondence 10/3/1988 - 12/12/1990 (Box 4)
  - Burke/Lee, A Joint Venture Site Selection Study February, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Mahan and Smith Correspondence 3/13/1984 - 1 1/27/1990 (Box 4)
  - Construction Reports 7/7/1989 - 12/14/1991 (Box 4)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Laboratory Concrete Testing 7/24/1989 - 5/22/1990 (Box 4)
  - Todd Hall Terrace 5/17/1990 - 11/1/1990 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #6 11/1/1990 - 1/7/1999 (Box 4)
  - Henry Klein Partnership General Correspondence #7 10/1/1990 - 1/7/1999 (Box 4)
  - Henry Klein Partnership Contract File C07860 1/1/1984 - 5/31/1991 (Box 4)
  - C.D. Contractors General Correspondence #3 9/1/1990 - 5/19/1993 (Box 4)
  - C.D. Contractors Contract File #2 3/29/1990 - 1/25/1991 (Box 4)
  - Rejected Bids - Bid Date 4/25/1989 (Box 4)
  - Schematic Design Brochure November, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Building Program Statement December, 1983 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #5 3/1/1990 - 10/31/1990 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #4 8/1/1989 - 2/28/1990 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #3 1/1/1989 - 7/31/1989 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #2 7/1/1984 - 12/31/1988 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondence #1 11/1/1982 - 6/30/1984 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #6 4/1/1990 - 9/30/1990 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #5 11/1/1989 - 3/31/1990 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #4 7/1/1989 - 10/31/1989 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #3 1/1/1989 - 6/30/1989 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #2 1/1/1985 - 12/31/1988 (Box 5)
  - Henry Klein Architects General Correspondence #1 11/1/1982 - 6/30/1984 (Box 5)
  - C.D. Contractors General Correspondence #2 2/1/1990 - 8/31/1990 (Box 5)
  - C.D. Contractors General Correspondence #1 5/31/1989 - 1/31/1990 (Box 5)
  - C.D. Contractors Contract File #1 C09729 6/1/1989 - 3/31/1990 (Box 5)
- Building 0088 - WSU Children's Center
  - Budget (Box 6)
  - Environ mental Impact Statement (Box 6)
  - Regents Reports (Box 6)
  - Mahan and DeSalvo Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Gifford Consultants Geotechnical Report (Box 6)
  - Building Committee (Box 6)
  - Constniction Reports (Box 6)
  - General ColTespondence #3 (Box 6)
  - Tsang Partnership General ColTespondence #4 (Box 6)
  - Tsang Partnership Contract File CO10799 (Box 6)
  - Pacific Crest Contractors, Inc. General Correspondence #2 (Box 6)
  - Pacific Crest Contractors Contract File #2 CO 11340 (Box 6)
  - Child Care Facility Playground Log #105378 General Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Child Care Facility Playground Tsang Partnership General Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Child Care Facility Playground R.A. Co. General Correspondence (Box 6)
  - Child Care Facility Playground R.A. Co. Contract File CO11727 (Box 6)
  - Pacific Crest Contractors Pending Change Proposals (Box 6)
  - Rejected Bids - Bid Date 3/25/1993 (Box 6)
  - General Correspondence #2 (Box 6)
  - General Correspondence #1 (Box 6)
  - Tsang Partnership General Correspondence #3 7/1/1993 - 12/31/1993 (Box 7)
  - Tsang Partnership General Correspondence #2 8/1/1992 - 6/30/1993 (Box 7)
  - Tsang Partnership General Correspondence #1 9/1/1991 - 7/31/1992 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Crest Contractors General Correspondence #1 3/1/1993 - 12/31/1994 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Crest Contractors Contract File #1 CO11340 3/25/1993 - 8/25/1993 (Box 7)
- Telecommunications
  - Budget 8/31/1987 - 11/10/1989 (Box 7)
  - Regents Reports (empty folder) (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence #3 8/1/1990 - 6/20/1991 (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence #2 3/1/1988 - 9/30/1990 (Box 7)
  - General Correspondence #1 12/1/1986 - 2/29/1988 (Box 7)
  - Peat Marwick Main and Co. General Correspondence 5/20/1988 (Box 7)
  - Peat Marwick Main and Co. Contract File C09206 2/26/1988 - 2/29/1988 (Box 7)
- Building 0680 - University Housing Apartment Project (Yakama Village)
  - Budget 1/12/1995 - 12/8/1995 (Box 8)
  - Environmental linpact Statement 5/19/1994 - 6/24/1994 (Box 8)
  - Regents 1/18/1994 - 3/8/1996 (Box 8)
  - Attorney General Correspondence 1/31/1994 - 8/25/1994 RESTRICTED (Box 8)
  - Issues and Claims 5/26/1994 - 1 1/2/1995 RESTRICTED (Box 8)
  - S.R. 270 Issues 5/3/1995 - 10/18/1995 (Box 8)
  - Burke/Lee Correspondence 5/25/1994 - 6/16/1994 (Box 8)
  - Don Brigham Plus Associates Correspondence 6/12/1995 - 6/29/1995 (Box 8)
  - Robert Fossatti Associates 8/18/1994 - 7/23/1996 (Box 8)
  - HCI Howard Consultants Geotechnical Engineers 9/9/1994 - 6/21/1995 (Box 8)
  - Contractor Field Reports 9/16/1994 - 10/23/1995 (Box 8)
  - Walsh Daily Construction Reports 9/1994 - 6/1995 (Box 8)
  - Wyatt - Jaykim Engineers Concrete Testing 9/26/1994 - 5/26/1995 (Box 8)
  - E-mail General Correspondence 3/22/1994 - 2/28/1995 (Box 8)
  - General Correspondence #3 1/1 1/1995 - 3/25/1998 (Box 8)
  - The ORB Organization Submittals 8/30/1994 - 10/7/1994 (Box 8)
  - The ORB Organization Construction Meeting Minutes 9/15/1994 - 6/29/1995 (Box 8)
  - The ORB Organization General Correspondence #3 12/13/1994 - 1 1/3/1995 (Box 8)
  - The ORB Organization Contract File #2 CO11640 10/10/1995 - 12/22/1995 (Box 8)
  - Walsh Construction Company General Correspondence #2 8/1/1995 - 8/15/1997 (Box 8)
  - Walsh Construction Company Contract File #2 COl 1778 8/23/1995 - 12/8/1995 (Box 8)
  - Punch Lists 6/6/1995 - 7/24/1995 (Box 8)
  - Pending Change Proposals 9/24/1994 - 9/27/1994 (Box 8)
  - Kruegel - McAllister Residence Halls Infonnation (Box 9)
  - Step 2: Design Competition 6/7/1994 - 8/31/1994 (Box 9)
  - Reference Letters 5/13/1994 - 5/16/1994 (Box 9)
  - Ledcor Industries General Correspondence 8/1994 (Box 9)
  - Rejected Bid Summaries - Bid Date 7/22/1994 (Box 9)
  - General Correspondence #1 9/1/1994 - 12/31/1994 (Box 9)
  - The ORB Organization, Inc. General Correspondence #2 9/1/1994 - 11/30/1994 (Box 9)
  - The ORB Organization, Inc. General Correspondence #1 4/1/1994 - 8/31/1994 (Box 9)
  - The ORB Organization, Inc. Contract File #1 CO11640 3/25/1994 - 6/30/1995 (Box 9)
  - Walsh Construction Company General Correspondence #1 8/1/1994 - 7/31/1995 (Box 9)
  - Walsh Construction Company Contract File #1 CO11778 8/1/1994 - 6/30/1995 (Box 9)
  - Punch Lists #1 5/22/1995 - 6/15/1995 (Box 9)
  - SR 270/WSU Entrance Project/University Housing Project Memo 12/16/1994 (Box 9)
  - Washington State University Design Build Student Housing Proposal (Box 9)
  - R.G. Nelson, Architect, and Northwest Architectural Company 5/17/1994 (Box 9)
  - URS Consultants, Inc - Statement of Qualifications 2/21/1994 (Box 9)
  - Design West Architects Statement of Qualifications 2/18/1994 (Box 9)
  - Dames and Moore Statement of Qualifications 2/21/1994 (Box 9)
  - CMA Project Management, Inc. Statement of Qualifications 2/21/1994 (Box 10)
  - Draft RFQ from ORB Organization 4/12/1994 (Box 10)
  - The ORB Organization, Inc. Statement of Qualifications 4/17/1994 (Box 10)
  - The ORB Organization, Inc. Draft Proposal and General Requirements 5/12/1994 (Box 10)
  - Walsh Construction and Michael and Kuhns Statement of Qualifications 5/17/1994 (Box 10)
  - Ledcor Industries Inc. Design/Build Information 5/17/1994 (Box 10)
  - CTS Engineers, Inc. Traffic Study 5/1994 (Box 10)
  - DEl Electrical Consultants Electrical Calculations and Specifications 9/1994 (Box 10)
  - Burke/Lee Environmental Checklist 5/12/1994 (Box 10)
  - Walsh Construction Co. Storm Water Pollution Prevention Program 8/26/1994 (Box 10)
  - Budgetary Estimate of Telecommunications Installation 6/2/1994 (Box 10)
  - Draft copy of General Conditions for WA State Facility Construction (Box 10)
  - Draft copy of Modifications to General Conditions (Box 10)
  - WSU 1994 Design/Build Housing Draft Program 5/6/1994 (Box 10)
  - WSU 1994 Design/Build Housing Draft Part 1 of 2 5/20/1994 (Box 10)
  - WSU 1994 Design/Build Housing Drat Par 2 of 2 5/20/1994 (Box 10)
  - Dave Smith's Project Notebook (Cost Estimates, Regents Info, Emergency various dates (Box 10)
  - Contacts, Sub - Contractor Info, Design/Build Firms, RFQ/RFP (Box 10)
  - Schedule, Telecomm and Trans, Sanitary Sewer, Comments, Submittals, Miscellaneous, Contracts, SR 270) (Box 10)
- Building #816 - Food and Human Nutrition Facility Phase II
  - Budget 9/25/1987 - 4/13/1993 (Box 11)
  - Regents 1/3/1989 - 5/7/1993 (Box 11)
  - AGRA Earth and Environmental CO11569 7/11/1994 - 9/19/1994 (Box 11)
  - Burke/Lee, A Joint Venture 4/18/1989 - 10/17/1989 (Box 11)
  - Mahan and DeSalvo 2/7/1989 - 1/12/1990 (Box 11)
  - Gifford Consultants Geotechnical Report 2/11/1991 (Box 11)
  - Building Committee 1/17/1989 - 6/15/1993 (Box 11)
  - Construction Reports 6/12/1990 - 6/9/1992 (Box 11)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Laboratory Concrete Testing Reports 5/15/1990 - 7/27/1994 (Box 11)
  - Wyatt - Jaykim Engineers Concrete Testing Reports 10/29/1987 - 9/22/1988 (Box 11)
  - Test Reports 10/14/1988 - 11/6/1989 (Box 11)
  - Creamery Grout Files 2/24/1993 - 4/17/1997 (Box 11)
  - Creamery Equipment #2 11/3/1992 - 4/7/1994 (Box 11)
  - Equipment Lists 5/16/1991 - 1/14/1992 (Box 11)
  - Fluid Engineering Correspondence 8/5/1987 - 8/2/1990 (Box 11)
  - Grant Applications 6/4/1989 - 1/11/1995 (Box 11)
  - General Correspondence #10 9/2/1993 - 8/28/1995 (Box 11)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence 8/3/1993 - 12/19/1996 (Box 11)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Contract File #2 C09293 9/20/1990 - 5/14/1996 (Box 11)
  - Shea Construction General Correspondence #2 5/10/1993 - 10/4/1996 (Box 11)
  - Shea Construction Contract File #4 CO10174 11/14/1991 - 3/24/1993 (Box 11)
  - Monroe Machinery and Supplies Contract File #2 CO10739 10/5/1992 - 6/2/1993 (Box 11)
  - Pending Change Proposals 5/14/1990 - 6/19/1992 (Box 11)
  - Statements of Compliance 5/29/1990 (Box 12)
  - Rejected Bids - Bid Date 3/29/1990 (Box 12)
  - Creamery Equipment #1 6/6/1991 - 11/2/1992 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #9 7/1/1992 - 7/31/1993 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #8 1/2/1992 - 6/30/1992 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #7 8/1/1991 - 12/31/1991 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #6 3/1/1991 - 7/31/1991 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #5 10/1/1990 - 2/28/1991 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #4 5/1/1990 - 9/30/1990 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #3 1/1/1990 - 4/30/1990 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #2 1/1/1989 - 12/31/1989 (Box 12)
  - General Correspondence #1 7/1/1987 - 12/31/1988 (Box 12)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #9 6/1/1992 - 7/3 1/1993 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #8 10/1/1991 - 5/31/1992 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #7 2/1/1991 - 9/30/1991 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #6 8/1/1990 - 1/31/1991 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General ColTespondence #5 5/1/1990 - 7/31/1990 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General ColTespondence #4 2/1/1990 - 4/30/1990 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #3 7/1/1989 - 1/31/1990 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #2 1/1/1989 - 6/30/1989 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company General Correspondence #1 7/1/1987 - 12/31/1988 (Box 13)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Contract File #1 C09293 7/12/1988 - 8/27/1990 (Box 14)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. General Correspondence File #1 4/1/1990 - 3/31/1993 (Box 14)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. Contract File #3 CO10174 6/1/1991 - 10/2/1991 (Box 14)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. Contract File #2 CO10174 4/2/1991 - 6/18/1991 (Box 14)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. Contract File #1 CO10174 3/22/1990 - 3/1/1991 (Box 14)
  - Monroe Machinery and Supplies Creamery Installation Contract #1 CO10739 9/1/1991 - 8/31/1992 (Box 14)
  - Creamery Installation Rejected Bids - Bid Date 8/24/1991 (Box 14)
  - Rejected General Bids - Bid Date 9/10/1987 (Box 14)
  - Rejected Electrical Bids - Bid Date 9/3/1987 (Box 14)
  - Rejected Mechanical Bids - Bid Date 9/3/1987 (Box 14)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Design Development Review Comments 12/7/1989 (Box 14)
  - Pacific Testing Laboratories Statement of Qualifications 12/18/1989 (Box 14)
  - Perspective Sketch, Site Plan, Floor Plans 8/30/1994 (Box 14)
  - Photographs in blue notebook June, 1994 (Box 14)
  - AGRA Earth and Environmental Evaluation of Epoxy Grout 10/19/1994 (Box 14)
  - Gifford Consultants, Inc. Geotechnical Report 4/18/1989 (Box 14)
  - Creamery Installation Bid Set Specifications (2) 6/28/1991 (Box 14)
  - Builders' Hardware and Supply Company Schedule of Finish Hardware 4/22/1992 (Box 14)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Design Development Presentation April, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Design Development Phase November, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Schematic Design Phase 6/26/1986 (Box 14)
  - FHN Phase II Building Program Master Copy May, 1988 (Box 14)
  - APV Crepaco, Inc. Creamery Contractor Bid 3/21/1990 (Box 14)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Addendum #1 3/8/1990 (Box 15)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Addendum #2 3/16/1990 (Box 15)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Addendum #3 3/20/1990 (Box 15)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Addendum #4 3/23/1990 (Box 15)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. Requests For Clarification 5/11/1990 - 10/10/1991 (Box 15)
  - Northwest Architectural Company Clarifications (Box 15)
  - Change Proposals 4/26/1990 - 2/10/1992 (Box 15)
  - Dave Smith FSHN Creamery Items from Notebook - General Correspondence (Box 15)
  - Dairy Equipment, and Equipment Bids (Box 15)
  - Dave Smith FSHN Items from Notebook - A/E Fees, Budget, Equipment/Furnishings, Federal Grants, Fixed Equipment, General Correspondence (Box 15)
  - Physical Plant, Project Stats, Regents, Schedules, Telecom Cable, Telecom Center, 95% Review Comments, Review Comments (Box 15)
- Building #1500 - Dairy Forage Facility Phase II, Buckley., WA
  - Budget 9/30/1991 - 9/28/1995 (Box 16)
  - Environmental Impact Statement 9/21/1992 - 12/21/1992 (Box 16)
  - Regents 3/24/1989 - 11/3/1994 (Box 16)
  - Bradley - Noble Geotechnical Committee 4/22/1994 (Box 16)
  - Burke/Lee Correspondence 5/13/1992 (Box 16)
  - Construction Materials Testing Laboratories 3/22/1994 - 10/19/1994 (Box 16)
  - Building Committee 9/25/1987 - 1/20/1993 (Box 16)
  - Water Line Upsize General Correspondence 2/16/1993 - 9-14-95 (Box 16)
  - General Correspondence 3/3/1993 - 9/24/1997 (Box 16)
  - The BJSS Group General Correspondence #2 1/24/1994 - 8/7/1995 (Box 16)
  - The BJSS Group Contract File #2 CO10845 12/1/1993 - 5/31/1995 (Box 16)
  - John Korsmo Construction, Inc. General Correspondence 12/14/1993 - 2/5/1996 (Box 16)
  - John Korsmo Construction, Inc. COl1557 11/17/1993 - 11/1/1995 (Box 16)
  - Rejected Bid Summaries Bid Date 7/1/1993 (Box 16)
  - Rejected Bid Summaries ReBid Date 11/18/1993 (Box 16)
  - General Correspondence #1 6/13/1990 - 12/21/1992 (Box 16)
  - The BJSS Group General Correspondence #1 11/26/1991 - 12/12/1993 (Box 16)
- Building 9500 - Tri-Cities University Center Addition
  - Master Planning various dates (Box 17)
  - Budget 8/31/1987 - 4/6/1993 (Box 17)
  - Regents Reports 9/2/1988 - 1/8/1992 (Box 17)
  - Burke/Lee Correspondence 1/6/1988 - 12/10/1990 (Box 17)
  - Mahan and DeSalvo Correspondence 4/14/1989 - 1/22/1990 (Box 17)
  - Concrete Testing 7/19/1990 - 3/29/199 1 (Box 17)
  - General Correspondence #9 7/8/1992 - 9/23/1993 (Box 17)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #15 2/1/1992 - 11/9/1992 (Box 17)
  - McKinley Gordon Contract File #3 CO9110 9/11/1992 (Box 17)
  - Hazen and Clark General Correspondence #2 10/1/1991 - 3/31/1993 (Box 17)
  - Hazen and Clark Contract File #7 CO10126 11/20/1991 - 2/17/1993 (Box 17)
  - Pending Change Proposals 11/26/1990 - 9/11/1991 (Box 17)
  - Rejected Electrical Bids - Bid Date 3/13/1990 (Box 17)
  - Rejected Mechanical Bids - Bid Date 3/13/1990 (Box 17)
  - Rejected General Bids - Bid Date 3/20/1990 (Box 17)
  - General Correspondence #8 9/1/1991 - 12/31/1992 (Box 17)
  - General Correspondence #7 4/1/1991 - 8/31/1991 (Box 17)